# **YEN HUNG LIN**

----

hello@yenhunglin.com yenhunglin.com

# **SKILLS**

### Experience in Brand, Visual and UI Design

Brand Design Print/Digital Design Packaging Design Motion Design Icon Design Banner Design

App/Web Design UI Library Mgmt. Wireframing App prototyping

# **Computer Programs**

Photoshop Illustrator InDesign

After Effects

Sketch Invision Zeplin -Jira

#### **Scripting Languages**

HTML CSS

Basic JS
Basic Framer X

## Languages

Engish Mandarin Chinese Taiwanese

# SELECTED RECOMMENDATIONS

#### Heidi Bullock // Chief Marketing Officer at Tealium

I feel very fortunate to have worked with Jeff. He is incredibly talented and can take a high level marketing concept and breath life into it. Jeff is also a unique talent because he is outstanding at UX as well, so companies can have a cohesive feel across external marketing and product. Jeff is thoughtful and responds well to feedback. He is someone I would hire again!

## Brandon Redlinger // Head of Growth, Engagio

Jeff is a phenomenal visual, UI, and UX designer. When he first came to Engagio, he was a contractor, but he was so good, we had to hire him full time. He does excellent work, he's fast, and he always has a great attitude. Working with both marketing and product, he developed consistent branding and experiences that we previously lacked. And his ability to go from conceptualization to rapid prototyping to review of the finished product while meeting the design requirements made him a highly valuable member of the team.

#### SELECTED EXPERIENCES

### **Engagio** // San Mateo, CA 2018-Present, Visual Designer

- Marketing Team: Collaborate on print, web, and motion designs. Define the brand system and translate the vibe of our brand into our products.
- Product Team: Work with PM, UX, and engineers to define the visual systems and the interactive elements of our app. Redefine and maintain UI library.

## MOCACARE // SF, CA + Taipei, Taiwan 2017-2018, Visual, UI/UX Designer

- Marketing Team: Work on digital and print designs.
   Projects include MOACuff package, user manual redesign, 2017 and 2018 holiday web banner designs.
- Product Team: Work on user research-based visual designs for MOCACARE app icons redesign and app pairing experience redesign.

# HTC // SF, CA + Taipei, Taiwan 2014-2015, Visual, Package Designer

- Participate in design process of HTC Vive and HTC 10 package design. Participate in 2015 visual design language conception with both packaging and industrial design team.
- Work with HTC innovation team on HTC 10 animation for internal presentation.
- Accompany designers to factories in Taiwan, meet with vendors to study new packaging materials, and build good work relationships with vendors.

# San Francisco Art Institute // SF, CA 2014, Graphic Design Intern

 Work with internal marketing team on weekly event poster designs, gallery show invitation designs, school publications, and school event photo documentation.

## EDUCATION

#### California College of the Arts

2013, BFA in Graphic Design